

Diego Zito

UX DESIGNER | MOTION DESIGNER | FRONT END FANATIC

DZ https://diegozito.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/diegozito/



WORK EXPERIENCE

Barcelona, ES

2018 - 2018

UX|UI TA - Ironhack

Teacher Assistant for 3 full time bootcamps. Aided over 40+ students in the learning of Design Thinking Methodologies, Information Architecture, interaction Design , Agile Methodologies and Web Development. Classes Thought

- -Principle Course (Animation and Microinteractions)
- Information Architecture (Onboarding & Forms)

Barcelona, ES

2017 - 2018

BI & Design Internship - The Bullitt Agency

Designed Artist Material for Marketing and Branding Purposes. Created company newsletter. Aided with the logistics of over 20+ Artists.

Miami, USA 2014 - 2016

Logistics & Production Mangament -III Points Music Festival

Oversaw the travel and logistics of over 40+ artists. Assisted with implementing business partenrships with different brands: Redbull, Monster & Heineken

Miami, USA 2015 - 2016

Graphic Design & Front End Internship -Lost in the Fold Digital Agency

Assisted with implementing a digital strategy for small businesses focused on the hospitality industry. Over 10 projects.

Frameworks: Illustrator, Photoshop, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Wordpress.

EDUCATION

Spain, ES Sep'15 - today

Miami, USA Jun'12 - Jan'15

Ironhack

UX|UI DesignMaster Bootcamp

Florida International University

BBs Business Administration | BS Hospitality Managment



SOFTWARE & FRAMEWORKS

Sketch
Principle
Invision
Adobe Comp
Adobe Indesign
HTML
CSS
Javascript
Bootstrap

PROFESIONAL SKILLS

Design Sprints
White Boarding
Prototyping
Wireframing
AB Testing
Interaction-Design
Animation

Visual -Communication Entrepeneurship Business Strategy Communication

Agile

Team Player Leadership

Time Managment

Ableton Live



HOBBIES













ABOUT ME

I am a UX|UI Designer based in Barcelona, Spain.

I am a creator with a strategic and entrepreneurial mind focused on User Experience and Front end fameworks. I like to inspire people by bringing them together in building digital products or services through creativy and growth.

I am passionate in what I do. I feel comfortable in dynamic and constantly evolving work environments

My Life is based on 3 principles

- Work smart not hard
- Treat others how you want to be treated
- Never Stop Learning



PERSONAL

NAME: Diego Zito
BIRTHDAY: 16th May' 91
COUNTRY: Venezuela

MOBILE: +34-699885435

EMAIL: contact@diegozito.com



Languages

Spanish Native Speaker English Native Speaker Italian Moderate



Latest Projects

Neigbhorly - UX | UI Study Case Second Chance - UX | UI Study Case Global Players - Concept App Gourmeasy - UX | UI Study Case